ibooking.com 2013-05-20

# Online Ticketing and Booking Solutions from iBooking.com

Privacy

This statement discloses the privacy practices for the entire web site. 

iBooking Limited. ("iBooking Limited") may collect implicit information on an anonymous basis from users who visit our web site, for aggregate statistical analysis and site customization. Implicit information is data that we can gather about the user without asking them. Importantly, aggregate statistical analysis means that iBooking Limited reviews trends based on information as a whole, but does not do so in an effort to identify the individual identity of the visitor to its site.   

We also may solicit email for site feedback, business development, press inquiries, and human resources inquiries. In select instances, this information may be shared with reputable third companies. However, iBooking Limited does not disclose human resource information solicited from our Web site to third parties or affiliates. 

When you use our email feature to email another individual any content on our site, such as a case study, we may collect information about the email sender and the recipient. We may use this information to email our quarterly newsletter or other iBooking Limited information from time to time. We will not share this information with any third parties or affiliates.

Any personal information that you voluntarily provide to us, such as site registration information, will be collected and used by us on an internal basis only. Unless we tell you otherwise at the point on the site where the information is collected, we do not share any personal information about you with third parties or affiliates.

IP addresses may be logged to track a user's session. An IP address is the unique numerical identity of your computer. When we "log" an IP address, it means that our Web site associates a visit or series of visits to that unique numerical identity. iBooking Limited also uses cookies in order to assist in aggregate statistical analysis and sometimes provide site customization based on anonymous session tracking. In other words, iBooking Limited uses cookies to determine trends for users as a whole, but not as means to learn about your individual identity. Cookies, by themselves, cannot be used to determine the actual identity of users. On their own, they can be used to identify a computer, but not who is using that computer. Because of this, if iBooking Limited customizes the site based on cookies, we won't know who you are unless you tell us. 

iBooking Limited collects the visitor's domain name (e.g. whether the user is logged on from foo.com), referral data (e.g. we record the last URL a user visited prior to clicking to iBooking Limited), as well as browser and platform type (e.g., a Microsoft browser on a Macintosh platform). We also count, track, and aggregate the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our sites (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within iBooking Limited.com). When and if iBooking Limited does present aggregated information to outside companies, no one would be able to identify you or contact you. 

We will never share your personal information with any third party without your consent, however, information may be transferred to another company if there is a sale or merger of iBooking Limited. Access to personal information is limited to our employees, contractors and agents with a need to access such information for the purposes set forth in this privacy policy. We will not use your personal information other than as set forth above without your consent. 

We reserve the right to change, add, or remove portions from this privacy policy at any time. However, if any change involves a plan to use your personal information in a way that differs from this privacy policy, we will first obtain your prior consent. When your consent is required for any action under this privacy policy, you agree that iBooking Limited may obtain your consent by an "opt-in" or "opt-out" method, or by other means (such as sending to you an email).
